clarkconnect.com 2004-12-07

# About Us - Legal - Privacy Policy

About Us Company History  Our Network Suva Technology

Legal Overview Privacy Policy UDRP gTLD Registration Terms of Service Gateway Antivirus

|   |   
|  | 

**We don't sell or give away your name, mail address, e-mail address, phone number, or any other personal information to anyone!**  
  
---|---  
  
Point Clark Networks protects any information you share with us. If you do not want to have customer information in our database, we will delete this information at anytime.  Contact us at [privacy@clarkconnect.com](mailto:privacy@clarkconnect.com).

* * *

###  Long Version

Point Clark Networks has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.  The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact and demographic information.  We use this information: 

\- to deliver our services!  
\- for diagnostics,   
\- to send critical notices to the user,  
\- to contact the visitor when necessary. 

We do not sell or give away your name, mail address, e-mail address, phone number, or any other personal information. However, information may be shared with advertisers on an **aggregate** basis - e.g. we may tell an advertiser that 30% of our users manage Cobalt products. 

This site contains links to other sites.  Point Clark Networks is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Please note:** as we add more software and services, additions or changes may be made to this policy. 

###  Security

| 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the customer information under our control.  
  
---|---  
  
### Choice/Opt-Out

Point Clark Networks provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications.  This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database. 

  * Send e-mail to [privacy@clarkconnect.com](mailto:privacy@clarkconnect.com)
  * Account configuration on the website

###  Cookies  

We use cookies to personalize your visit to our site.  We do not use DoubleClick-like tactics.  A cookie is simply a small data file we place on your computer's hard drive when you first visit us.  This file contains a unique number that helps us identify you when you return to our site.  Allowing us to create a cookie on your hard drive will not give us or any other site access to the rest of your computer's hard drive, and only we'll be able to read the cookie that our site creates.  

|   
  
---|---  
  
###  Correct/Update

Point Clark Networks gives users the following options for modifying information previously provided. 

  * Send e-mail to [privacy@clarkconnect.com](mailto:privacy@clarkconnect.com)
  * Account configuration on the website

###  Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of Point Clark Networks, or your dealings with this web site, you can contact [privacy@clarkconnect.com](mailto:privacy@clarkconnect.com).

Cheers,  
The Point Clark Networks team.
